=Remnants of Gold=
(Adapted from Gu Long's
"Flying Eagle over the Great Land")
(The main characters
in this drama are fictional)
=Episode 10=
Which of you
is the Qin Demon of Mount Pingfeng?
Everyone who comes
asks the same question.
I am the Qin, and he is the Demon.
The same goes
the other way around.
We live on Mount Pingfeng.
Let's cut to the chase.
How much gold will it take
to hire you two?
You need to apologize first.
When you came in just now,
I asked you to wait,
but you walked
right into the inner room.
What if I were inside naked?
Just apologize.
It doesn't cost a thing.
My mistake.
Alright, you men go ahead and talk.
I won't interrupt.
How much gold will it take
to hire you two?
How much do you have?
You're not asking what the job is?
However much gold you have,
that's how much work we do.
Our expenses are very high.
We can't help it.
Just this guqin alone
costs 50 taels of gold.
And then there are rouge, perfume,
and hot spring baths daily...
One hundred taels
of gold.
Do you have it?
Is there any more?
One hundred taels is a lot.
Tie Futu,
where are those fierce men of yours
who usually follow you wherever you go?
I hear you came here alone.
Have you fallen so low?
What's wrong with me being alone?
What's wrong with being alone?
Yet you still came looking for us.
You should know that we are expensive.
Who is actually in charge?
Are 100 taels of gold still not enough?
It's more than enough.
Is your Soft Hedgehog Armor
made of gold?
Yes.
Can you give it to me?
I came to ask for your help.
It doesn't mean I'm afraid of you.
It's useless anyway.
Two notes from my guqin
are worth more than it.
Pretend I was never here.
Asking you to hand over the armor
was such a hassle.
How can you take out this hundred taels
and then just take it back?
What sorcery
does this guqin have?
It seems your internal power
is quite ordinary.
With our guqin music,
the higher one's martial skill,
the harder it hits.
Ordinary people with no internal power
aren't affected at all.
If we encounter ordinary people,
we can only reason with them nicely.
The better their martial arts,
the angrier we get instead.
Why don't you tell us
what this is about first?
Retrieve 300,000 taels of gold.
They say Gansu
has 300,000 taels of gold.
Do you know where they are hidden?
Ganzhou,
under the Shaanxi Branch
Regional Military Commission.
Where exactly?
Under the Regional
Military Commission Yamen.
Who told you?
Zhang Luyao.
A woman.
I killed her entire family.
What was her name?
Zhang Luyao.
If I were her,
I would skin you alive
and drink your blood.
Tie Futu,
have you lost your mind?
You haven't met Zhang Luyao.
She knows where the gold is.
She wants you dead,
which is why she told you
that 300,000 taels of gold
is hidden in the Regional
Military Commission Yamen.
Don't laugh.
Thirty years ago,
when the gold was buried,
there was no Commander-in-Chief yet.
Tie Futu,
are you insane?
Someone finally told me
where the gold is.
I must...
How do we get into the Yamen?
How do we get out?
And how do we get
the gold out of the underground?
That's why I'm asking you.
I heard you were decisive and ruthless.
I never expected you to be a lunatic.
Have you always been like this?
I've never been
to the Regional
Military Commission Yamen before.
Right.
We have not been there.
For 100 taels of gold
plus a Soft Hedgehog Armor,
Tie Futu asked us to go to
the Regional Military Commission Yamen
to take a look around.
It's only fair that we go.
Even if it's fair, we shouldn't go.
He's crazy, but we aren't.
Then, we'll have to return
these 100 taels of gold and
the Soft Hedgehog Armor to him?
Return these...
You obviously don't want to.
If you don't want to,
neither do I.
How much gold can one horse carry?
Three thousand two hundred taels.
What about four thousand taels?
A fine horse could manage.
Look, we ride two horses into
the Regional Military Commission Yamen,
and when we come out,
four thousand taels per horse,
and eight thousand taels for two horses.
Wouldn't the Yamen become
a temple of the God of Wealth?
And wouldn't the Commander-in-Chief
become the God of Wealth himself?
Sounds great.
Yan,
you've gone crazy, too.
Isn't my crazy side
what you like about me?
Deputy,
may I ask...
First, we go to Shiquan Fort.
Shiquan Fort isn't part
of Liangzhou anymore.
Further west,
we go to Wusu Sea to find
the 300,000 taels of gold.
What happens after we find it?
Everyone gets rich.
How are we supposed to get rich?
We won't be returning to Liangzhou?
You can turn back right now.
Once we find the gold,
why would we ever go back?
Deputy,
I still have a wife
and kid back in Liangzhou.
Then go back
and spend the rest of your life
eating yellow sand with them.
Bana was my father.
When my father died,
he collapsed on top of you.
Shut up.
I saw his lips moving.
Weren't they moving?
I told you to shut up.
Did he say something to you?
Did he have a message
for you to pass to me?
My father surely
had something to tell me.
If you say one more word,
I'll run you through with my spear.
Does the General know
that we've been
following you all this way?
No, he doesn't.
So, we are
rebelling?
Have you lost your mind?
Coroner,
you can head back.
Say one more word,
and you won't make it out alive.
Keep moving forward.
You've come.
Bana's kid is here.
Take us to Wusu Sea.
I've guarded
300,000 taels of gold for 30 years.
Taking you to get it
just for the sake of a boy?
That's too easy.
Someone is going to take
the gold sooner or later anyway.
True enough.
If you can overcome my bow,
then you're the ones
meant to take the gold.
If you can't,
I'll just bury you all
and wait for the next group.
With just a single bow?
Let me show you what
the Liangzhou guards are capable of.
Form up.
Divine machinery.
Quick.
Shield wall. Form a shield wall!
Take him down.
Interesting.
Let me show you what I've got.
Don't move.
Step back.
Seventeen,
where's your father?
He's dead.
Who killed Bana?
Me.
I did.
I killed him.
So what?
That works out even better.
Saves us a lot of trouble.
The kid is still here.
I don't believe
you don't care about your guy's son.
Lad,
Miss Zhang asked me
to pass a message to you.
What did she say?
Pingping is dead.
Is there anything else?
Yes.
You liar.
Your eyes are so bright
and so pure.
Don't move.
I will go find Luyao.
Among everyone here,
you have the best martial skills.
Did that official
tell you to keep an eye on Seventeen?
Yes.
So if I make a move against him,
you'll kill Seventeen, right?
Yes!
Lad,
why?
Why, my foot!
My life belongs to the Deputy.
I kill whoever he tells me to kill.
Miss Zhang asked me not to hurt you
and to spare your life.
I promised her,
so I won't touch you,
and you don't touch Seventeen.
But you're going after the Deputy.
Yes.
If you dare touch the Deputy,
I'll kill him!
Lad,
don't make this hard for me.
Don't you make this hard for me!
Let's see if your spear is faster
or my arrow is.
Don't move.
Coroner,
Fang,
let's go back.
Go...
Go back.
Go.
The Deputy is right here.
Where are you going back to?
Brat, you are asking for death.
Deputy.
Attack!
Quick.
Go die!
I will kill...
Attack.
I'll kill you.
I...
I should have killed you long ago.
Does anyone else still want gold?
No.
We just want to live.
Lad,
Miss Zhang doted on you for nothing.
Seventeen.
Don't leave.
From now on,
call me Father.
Can I call you that anytime?
Call me that both in public and private.
Where are we going?
Wusu Sea.
To find your 16 other fathers.
Is Wusu Sea as good as Lieyang Well?
Why are you so chatty?
Wusu Sea
is covered in gold everywhere.
It's just like heaven.
Move.
I shouldn't have given you this spear.
Hou,
how did this happen?
The General is dead.
Who said that?
The General
won't die.
Neither will you, Deputy.
The General is dead.
Who said that?
Hou,
it seems
I can't see anymore.
Who is it that said
the General is dead?
Ha Bingzhong.
Deputy,
kill him.
If anyone says
you're dead,
I will
kill them.
Alright, I'll go kill him.
Bury me
a bit higher.
The higher,
the better.
A place
where I can see
Liangzhou.
Alright.
Deputy,
the General is dead?
Ready the horses.
Back to Liangzhou?
We can't go back.
Then, where to?
To Ganzhou.
Yes, sir.
Ready the horses!
- Yes, sir.
I want to see...
Take the horse back.
Riders have always dismounted
before entering the field.
Don't you know who I am?
Turn back now,
or I'll put down the horse.
I've always ridden straight in.
That was only because
General Ha allowed it back then.
Dismount and take it back.
Riding is not permitted
in the martial grounds.
I want to see the General.
Without General Ha's order,
no one sees the Commander-in-Chief.
Where is Ha Bingzhong?
In the accounting office.
Get out of the way.
General Ha.
Ha Bingzhong.
Are you crazy?
I'm here to settle accounts with you.
You found the gold?
Yes.
Thirty years ago,
it was buried right beneath
the Regional Military Commission Yamen.
Who told you that?
Zhang Luyao.
The woman you ordered me
to poison her family
and bring back.
It was the General who
ordered you to bring her back.
If the gold were buried under
the Regional Military Commission Yamen,
would the General
turn the place upside down to dig it up?
How could you believe
such words from Zhang Luyao?
If it were dug up, how much would I get?
How much would
the General even give you?
They said you came back alone.
Where are your guys?
They're all dead.
Zhang Luyao
killed them?
I shouldn't have let the woman return.
Where is Zhang Luyao now?
She's with the Embroidered
Uniform Guard officer from the Capital.
She knows everything.
What does she know?
Well...
She knows that the General ordered me
to poison all 27 members of her family!
She knows where the gold is!
She knows everything!
Tie Futu,
have you really gone mad?
If I tried to look
for the 300,000 taels of gold again,
then I'd truly be mad.
3,000 taels.
That's not much.
You have gold.
You want 3,000 taels?
Give me the gold,
and we can just drop
this whole matter.
Everything
is up to the General to decide.
If there's no gold,
I'll go find the Embroidered
Uniform Guard officer from the Capital.
Why are you looking for him?
To let the people in the Capital
know about the General's decision.
Go ahead and find him.
Really?
Futu, you can do whatever you want.
You've made the decision
for the General on this matter?
If the imperial court
finds out that the General...
Don't worry about the General.
(Shaanxi Branch
Regional Military Commission)
I'm here to see the Commander-in-Chief.
Who goes there?
Dismount!
Embroidered Uniform Guard
on official business.
Embroidered Uniform Guard?
What business?
Just asking
if the Commander-in-Chief
of Gansu is colluding with bandits
and perverting the law
for personal gain.
Report!
There's an Embroidered
Uniform Guard officer outside
who wants to investigate
the Commander-in-Chief.
I've risked my life for the General.
The General offered 200 taels of gold
for 27 lives of the Zhang family.
I have 20 men with me.
That's 100 taels per person.
Isn't that fair?
You can forget about
getting another single tael of gold.
Consider this matter over.
You must leave the Yamen now
and never come back.
The General
never knew who you were.
I have never seen you, either.
Now, leave.
I'm going to ask the General myself.
The General is asleep.
You say he's sleeping every single time.
The General has
been sleeping all this time.
When he wakes up,
I'll bring him his medicine.
Futu,
don't go looking for death.
I won't make a move.
All I need to do is shout.
General Ha.
Who is it?
A Capital Embroidered Uniform Guard
officer wants to see the General.
Where is he?
He's already at the drill grounds.
Tell him to wait. I'll be right over.
He says he wants to see
the Commander-in-Chief.
Understood.
Keep an eye on him.
Don't let him enter the rear courtyard.
Yes.
Open the gates.
Now,
the Embroidered Uniform Guard
officer is here.
There's no need to search for him, Futu.
When you see the Guard officer,
you can tell him
everything you know.
Let's see whether he rewards you first
or asks my soldiers
to take you down.
If you push me to a dead end,
I'll have no choice
but to fight to the death.
What can you gain
from fighting to the death?
At worst, I'll walk away with nothing.
How can you just leave empty-handed?
How about this?
Go to the drill grounds,
kill the Embroidered
Uniform Guard officer,
and I'll make the call for the General
to give you
150 taels of gold.
You must be thinking,
after I kill the Guard officer,
how am I supposed to
get out of the Yamen?
Come,
here you go.
150 taels of gold.
Futu, think about it.
Carrying
all this gold on you,
you'll surely be able to run faster.
What are you thinking about now?
Futu,
for half your life,
you've lived on the edge
as a fugitive.
Killing one more or one less person,
what difference does it make?
As long as you do this,
living in the great desert,
the General
will still remember your favor.
So just like that,
I walk out to the drill grounds
and start killing?
Of course not.
Of course I'll be going with you.
With my orders,
even moving around
will be much easier.
How long is this announcement
going to take?
The sun is about to set.
The Commander-in-Chief is inside?
Move.
Officer, please don't
make things difficult for us.
I am an Embroidered Uniform Guard
officer sent by the imperial court.
Tell the Commander-in-Chief
to come out and meet me!
I could hear
your voice from afar.
So that's how it is.
Officer,
how should I address you?
Are you the Commander-in-Chief?
I'm Ha Bingzhong,
a guerrilla commander.
The General
is sleeping inside.
This man
colluded with
the General to murder and rob.
Are you aware of this?
The General guards the Northwest.
Even if you are from
the Embroidered Uniform Guard,
don't speak nonsense.
I've said what I needed to say.
Tell the Commander-in-Chief
to come out and meet me.
Is the General someone
you can just see whenever you want?
So what if he guards the Northwest?
If he's guilty, he must answer for it.
All land under heaven
belongs to the King.
Yes.
You're right, Officer.
The villain is right here,
saving me the trouble of searching.
Arrest him.
This man
originally came to
see the General as well.
Now, he won't be able to.
If you want to arrest him,
then go ahead.
Arrest him!
Arrest him.
Please, Officer, arrest him.
What is the meaning of this?
Tie Futu,
the superior officer
ordered your arrest.
Surrender at once.
Arrest him.
Did you hear me?
Arrest this jerk!
Officer...
General Ha.
The Officer is no match for him.
I am a seventh-rank imperial
Embroidered Uniform Guard officer.
Have the twelve guards of
Gan-Liang all rebelled?
Arrest this jerk!
General Ha.
Are you okay, Officer?
Should we capture Tie Futu first?
(Preview of the Next Episode)
How do you think
we should close the case?
Gold,
1,200 taels.
Officer Pu,
pack them up well.
The General requests your presence.
Make way!
(May Divine Might Protect Us Forever)
=Remnants of Gold=